Wow Bartleby the courage sure did come
out good this season they sure look
delicious I must say they do look
rather scrumptious
they look so plump and juicy like your
butt cheeks I know they're for the
upcoming winter but I just can't hold
myself back go that is quite delicious I
think you'll have one more now come my
Beach we must hurry to the shack if we
are to sort the vegetables before winter
so my Beach I reckon you already take
the corn as well yes Bartleby all of the
corn has been picked I tried oh so hard
to please you
ha ha ha somebody must pay Todd did all
of that hard labor talk you out already
my juicy Beach well now that you mention
it I am kind of tired I guess but that
just won't do my fat lover we have much
left to do today if you slack off who
else will gather up the yummy veggies
yet I guess you're right Bartleby yes I
know now cam Beach let's take Ali
you
what is this oh sorry Bartleby I
guess I forgot to pick that one you'll
get it right away there's no need to
push yourself Beach I can do it myself
you